<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Volunteering on Agata</title>
    <link>https://agatakazakevic.github.io/Agataportfolio/post1/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Volunteering on Agata</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://agatakazakevic.github.io/Agataportfolio/post1/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Children tutoring</title>
      <link>https://agatakazakevic.github.io/Agataportfolio/post1/chapter-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agatakazakevic.github.io/Agataportfolio/post1/chapter-1/</guid>
      <description>“Is it correct?” Sophie looks up at me.
“Yes, it is. Great job!”
She sings happily, doing a little dance in her seat. Looking at her, I feel like dancing too. This was one of my five years-long volunteering sessions with an organization called “KTG”, which works with schools in low-income communities to match volunteer tutors with elementary school children. That afternoon, I was the Lithuanian language tutor, but years ago I didn&amp;rsquo;t have the needed help.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Naujininkai community club</title>
      <link>https://agatakazakevic.github.io/Agataportfolio/post1/chapter-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agatakazakevic.github.io/Agataportfolio/post1/chapter-3/</guid>
      <description>Ever since I was a child, I heard from my mother that I should be careful when coming home from school. When lessons were over, I did not want to leave school. Unfortunately, the reason was not the love for school, but the fear of going home because I lived in an unsafe area. My district, where I was born and lived for 15 years, is considered one of the most unsafe in Vilnius.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Volunteering at museum</title>
      <link>https://agatakazakevic.github.io/Agataportfolio/post1/chapter-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agatakazakevic.github.io/Agataportfolio/post1/chapter-2/</guid>
      <description>I have been volunteering at Energy and technology museum for almost a year. Growing up as a shy and self-contained person, I considered an activity that requires communication and teamwork skills very demanding for me. Picture a girl in the fourth class. When it’s her turn to speak, she is trembling so hard that the sheet in her hand shakes wildly. She rushes through her lines and falls back in relief.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
